<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[My Octopress Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/"/>
  <updated>2015-08-24T01:30:32-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Your Name]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog Week 10]]></title>
    <link href="http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/blog/2015/08/24/blog-week-10/"/>
    <updated>2015-08-24T00:56:23-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/blog/2015/08/24/blog-week-10</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>My blog for week 10 let me start by saying its been a very busy week for me to much on my hand to do and so little time running here running there like I&rsquo;m crazy. Plus the mac been acting up so much but I&rsquo;ve stayed calm and breathed.</p>

<p>Rails on bridge was fun if my mac would function correctly which is crazy because they even seemed to have a hard time with it and had no clue why it was working. It was super loud that day I had to put my headphones so I could concentrate on doing things and alot of people which scares me alot thats why I stayed in my spot most of the time, I know Im a little bit weird but thats just me at times.
I really enjoyed the Madison + Ruby conference it was awesome and super cool. Loved all the presentations they were really inspiring and motivational.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog Week 09]]></title>
    <link href="http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/blog/2015/08/16/blog-week-09/"/>
    <updated>2015-08-16T00:14:52-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/blog/2015/08/16/blog-week-09</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>My blog week 09 I loved class this week because I felt that I had some actual time to work on stuff that I still need to finish that I haven&rsquo;t had a chance to even get to without new stuff being thrown at me. I am
so thankful for alot of classmates that sit next to me we work great together and figure things out and are very helpful when one is struggling.
I was very scared about doing the Mock Interviews but now that its over and done now I feel a big relief.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog Week #1]]></title>
    <link href="http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/blog/2015/08/15/blog-week-number-1/"/>
    <updated>2015-08-15T22:07:41-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/blog/2015/08/15/blog-week-number-1</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog Week 08]]></title>
    <link href="http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/blog/2015/08/09/blog-week-08/"/>
    <updated>2015-08-09T23:57:14-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/blog/2015/08/09/blog-week-08</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This is my blog from week08 it&rsquo;s been a pretty crazy week driving myself insane trying to meet all the deadlines as much as possible with very little sleep to try and keep up. After my incident on Wednesday with four shots of expresso never again will I do that, it had me shaking, nausious and my blood pressure went sky high. I learned my lesson with that it made me feel super sick. This week I&rsquo;ve been multitasking at everything if I got stuck on something, I just jumped to another while I think about. I know for a fact that I can be very stuburn in getting an answer unless I get give up and then I ask for help.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog Week 07]]></title>
    <link href="http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/blog/2015/08/02/blog-week-07/"/>
    <updated>2015-08-02T23:50:01-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/blog/2015/08/02/blog-week-07</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>My blog post for week 07 its has been a crazy week I&rsquo;m at the point of giving up on this I feel like a total failer in here. No matter how much effort or determination I put in this class I it&rsquo;s not getting me no where. The more I see my report card, the more deppressing it gets. I feel so desapointed in seeing my report card its not even funny no more. I am trying my best to meet all these deadlines but it never seems enough and I dont like feeling this way it stressing me alot. Me and Code School are at the point of breaking up and taking a break it keeps clitching and acting up when I am puting the correct answer.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog Week 06]]></title>
    <link href="http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/24/blog-week-06/"/>
    <updated>2015-07-24T23:44:08-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/24/blog-week-06</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This is my blog post of week 6, its been an ok week so far. I&rsquo;ve been doing a little of everything trying to stay up to date with the due dates on stuff even though sometimes I think Im going crazy with so much stuff to be done and not have enough time for me personaly to relax. Even though I thought of quiting the class I am very determined to finish this class and try my 100% at this. I wanna thank everyone in the class that has helped me understand stuff into detail. I am having a little fun working with HTML stuff I learned from coode school and stuff I&rsquo;ve been doing on my own research. I&rsquo;m just praying that God get me thru this class to finish it.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog Week 05]]></title>
    <link href="http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/19/blog-week-05/"/>
    <updated>2015-07-19T23:35:24-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/19/blog-week-05</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This is my week05 blogpost it has been an intresting week. I felt a little lost working with javascript in the chapter02 but now that my former classmate Kathy has helped me understand it more but not at the point to feel comftable working with it alone. We started working with HTML and I enjoy working this much more because I feel like I understand it and is straight forward on what things need to be done. I loved working with codeschool. I feel I learned alot going thru codeschool with the tests.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog Week 04]]></title>
    <link href="http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/12/blog-week-04/"/>
    <updated>2015-07-12T23:27:47-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/12/blog-week-04</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This is my week 04 its been kind of very hectic and very confusing working on Chapter02. The many times in this chapter I felt lost and not knowing what I was doing nor why, but I have gotten help from a couple of my classmates that can explain to me stuff much more simple so I could understand this. I loved the activity you assigned each one of us to work on that was pretty cool and creative working with the Scrum Board.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog Week 03]]></title>
    <link href="http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/06/blog-week-03/"/>
    <updated>2015-07-06T23:07:12-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/06/blog-week-03</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In my third weeek I worked on chapter 02. We learned how to build statements which they contain expressions. I learned that putting statements after one another give you program runs from top to bottom, using conditional(if, else, and switch) and looping (while, do, and for) stgatements. I also learned about using Variables. I have also been practicing on my ipad Jvascript and how it works and why? I really am enjoying the app because I am being tested in what I&rsquo;m learning and if I font respond correctly I cant move forward.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog Week 02]]></title>
    <link href="http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/blog/2015/06/26/blog-week-02/"/>
    <updated>2015-06-26T22:47:09-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/blog/2015/06/26/blog-week-02</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This week #2 I have learned alot of things in JavaScript. we learned about four types of JavaScript which are: 1) Numbers 2) Strings 3) Booleans 4) Undefined Values</p>

<p>We worked with Arithmetic using special numbers, Strings, Unary operators, Boolean Values &amp; Logical operatores.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog Week]]></title>
    <link href="http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/blog/2015/06/19/first-post/"/>
    <updated>2015-06-19T16:47:51-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/blog/2015/06/19/first-post</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I&rsquo;m loving all the new things that we are learning in the class seems very intresting. Little by little I am starting to actully get some of this stuff.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
