<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[My Octopress Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/"/>
  <updated>2015-08-15T23:48:28-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Your Name]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog Week #1]]></title>
    <link href="http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/blog/2015/08/15/blog-week-number-1/"/>
    <updated>2015-08-15T22:07:41-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/blog/2015/08/15/blog-week-number-1</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog Week 06]]></title>
    <link href="http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/24/blog-week-06/"/>
    <updated>2015-07-24T23:44:08-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/24/blog-week-06</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This is my blog post of week 6, its been an ok week so far. I&rsquo;ve been doing a little of everything trying to stay up to date with the due dates on stuff even though sometimes I think Im going crazy with so much stuff to be done and not have enough time for me personaly to relax. Even though I thought of quiting the class I am very determined to finish this class and try my 100% at this. I wanna thank everyone in the class that has helped me understand stuff into detail. I am having a little fun working with HTML stuff I learned from coode school and stuff I&rsquo;ve been doing on my own research. I&rsquo;m just praying that God get me thru this class to finish it.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog Week 05]]></title>
    <link href="http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/19/blog-week-05/"/>
    <updated>2015-07-19T23:35:24-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/19/blog-week-05</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This is my week05 blogpost it has been an intresting week. I felt a little lost working with javascript in the chapter02 but now that my former classmate Kathy has helped me understand it more but not at the point to feel comftable working with it alone. We started working with HTML and I enjoy working this much more because I feel like I understand it and is straight forward on what things need to be done. I loved working with codeschool. I feel I learned alot going thru codeschool with the tests.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog Week 04]]></title>
    <link href="http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/12/blog-week-04/"/>
    <updated>2015-07-12T23:27:47-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/12/blog-week-04</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This is my week 04 its been kind of very hectic and very confusing working on Chapter02. The many times in this chapter I felt lost and not knowing what I was doing nor why, but I have gotten help from a couple of my classmates that can explain to me stuff much more simple so I could understand this. I loved the activity you assigned each one of us to work on that was pretty cool and creative working with the Scrum Board.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog Week 03]]></title>
    <link href="http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/06/blog-week-03/"/>
    <updated>2015-07-06T23:07:12-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/06/blog-week-03</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In my third weeek I worked on chapter 02. We learned how to build statements which they contain expressions. I learned that putting statements after one another give you program runs from top to bottom, using conditional(if, else, and switch) and looping (while, do, and for) stgatements. I also learned about using Variables. I have also been practicing on my ipad Jvascript and how it works and why? I really am enjoying the app because I am being tested in what I&rsquo;m learning and if I font respond correctly I cant move forward.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog Week 02]]></title>
    <link href="http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/blog/2015/06/26/blog-week-02/"/>
    <updated>2015-06-26T22:47:09-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/blog/2015/06/26/blog-week-02</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This week #2 I have learned alot of things in JavaScript. we learned about four types of JavaScript which are: 1) Numbers 2) Strings 3) Booleans 4) Undefined Values</p>

<p>We worked with Arithmetic using special numbers, Strings, Unary operators, Boolean Values &amp; Logical operatores.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog Week]]></title>
    <link href="http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/blog/2015/06/19/first-post/"/>
    <updated>2015-06-19T16:47:51-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://malysandrac.github.io/blog/blog/2015/06/19/first-post</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I&rsquo;m loving all the new things that we are learning in the class seems very intresting. Little by little I am starting to actully get some of this stuff.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
